<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X (U) (V1.1).smc</path>
		<name>Mega Man X</name>
		<desc>Near the end of his life, Dr. Light succeeds in creating the first of a new series of robots which will change the world. Able to think and make decisions, this new robot holds great danger as well as great possibilities. Fearful of the possible consequences of unleashing his creation on the world, Dr. Light decides to seal him in a capsule and test his systems until they are totally reliable. The future will have to decide his fate...

Released from the capsule by Dr. Cain, "X" is born into the world of the future where the robot rebellions are a thing of the past. But when Dr. Cain tries to implement Dr. Light's designs into a new series of Reploids, something goes hideously wrong. Now the future lies on the brink of destruction and a new Mega Man must emerge to face Sigma and his forces before the human race is wiped from the planet!

*12 Megs featuring 12 levels of action!
*New Powers, New Abilities!
*For 1 Player only.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mega Man X (U) (V1.1)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X 3 (U).smc</path>
		<name>Mega Man X3</name>
		<desc>Mega Man X and his trusty partner Zero have a new force to reckon with. Who or what has caused a riot of Mavericks to break out in the experimental utopia known as Doppler Town?

Named after the scientist reploid, Doppler Town was supposed to be a place where humans and reploids could live in harmony. After discovering a virus that was turning reploids to Mavericks, Doppler's anti-virus was a big success. But Doppler itself became infected with the virus and assembled a team to take out the Maverick Hunter Units. The Doppler Effect is about to unfold, with Mega Man X and Zero the only cure for the deadly virus!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mega Man X 3 (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mania (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Mickey Mania: The Timeless Adventures of Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>Mickey Mouse gets a chance to go down memory lane and walk through the timeless adventures he has lived. Mickey Mania is a platformer where all the levels are based on Mickey's most famous cartoons. The levels range about 75 years, starting off with "Steamboat Willie" and going all the way to "The Prince and the Pauper".

The gameplay consists mostly of jumping and marble throwing at enemies, with an occasional puzzle element.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mickey Mania (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat II (U) (V1.1).smc</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
		<desc>Following his failure to defeat Liu Kang in the first Mortal Kombat game, the evil sorcerer Shang Tsung begs his master, Shao Kahn, to spare his life. He tells Shao Kahn that the invitation for Mortal Kombat cannot be turned down, and if they hold it in Outworld, the Earthrealm warriors must attend. Kahn agrees to this plan, and even restores Tsung's youth. He then extends the invitation to Raiden, who gathers his warriors and takes them into Outworld. The new tournament is much more dangerous, as Shao Kahn has the home field advantage, and an Outworld victory will allow him to subdue Earthrealm.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mortal Kombat II (U) (V1.1)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man (U).smc</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man</name>
		<desc>In 1982, a sequel to the  incredibly popular Pac-Man was introduced in the form of his girlfriend, Ms. Pac-Man.  This sequel continued on the "eat the dots/avoid the ghosts" gameplay of the original game, but added new features to keep the title fresh.

Like her boyfriend, Ms. Pac-Man attempts to clear four various and challenging mazes filled with dots and ever-moving bouncing fruit  while avoiding Inky, Blinky, Pinky and Sue, each with their own personalities and tactics.  One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Ms. Pac-Man.

Ms. Pac-Man can turn the tables on her pursuers by eating one of the four Energizers located within the maze. During this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Ms. Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points. The Energizer power only lasts for a limited amount of time, as the ghost's eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Ms. Pac-Man again.

Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and the player will be treated to humorous intermissions showing the growing romantic relationship between Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man, leading all the way up to the arrival of "Junior".</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ms. Pac-Man (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Adventure Island (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Super Adventure Island</name>
		<desc>Master Higgins is back in his wildest and greatest adventure of all! His girlfriend, Jeannie Jungle, has been turned to stone by the evil Dark Cloak. Now he must leap into action to defeat the scores of guardian animals and monsters that protect the wicked wizard.
Join Master Higgins as he reaches new heights of adventure on his high flying skateboard. Speed through underground caves in a crazy mine car ride! Go from tropical shores to the belly of a whale - all in search of his final battle with the mad magician, Dark Cloak!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Adventure Island (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Produce</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Punch-Out!! (U).smc</path>
		<name>Super Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>Slug your way through the grueling and sweat-pounding matches of the Minor, Major and World Circuits. Dodge bone-bruising punches and dance to the top of the supreme Special Circuit. Face off against old favorites including Bear Hugger, Piston Hurricane, Bald Bull, Mr. Sandman and Super Macho Man plus a cast of new and weird challengers. With a right hook! Body blow! And precise quick jabs! The referee announces "Knock Out!" Your opponent lies face down as you win the title of Nintendo Video Boxing Association Champion!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Punch-Out!! (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario All-Stars (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Super Mario All-Stars</name>
		<desc>Revisit the magic and fun of the classic Super Mario Bros. series on your Super NES!  All the great Super Mario Bros. games for the NES have been powered up with 16-bit graphics and sound and collected on one super game pak.  As an added bonus, the previously unreleased “Lost Levels” are included.  These super challenging courses have never been available in this country until now!

* Four great games in one game pak!
* Battery backed memory saves up to 4 players’ progress through every game!
* Play alone or 2 players can alternate play!
* New 16-bit graphics, sound, and other surprises!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario All-Stars (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20181223T203009</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters (U).smc</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tournament Fighters</name>
		<desc>Trash the surf board and heave the 'za. It's a whole new breed of Turtles and they're fixated on fighting. We're dead serious, Tournament Fighters takes dude-on-dude demolition to new heights of intensity with 4 modes of pain-producing battles, deadly warriors, secret arenas, astounding graphics and sound effects that'll make you cringe! Clash with Krang-created clones of the Turtles, Casey Jones, April O'Neil, Ray Filet and Sisyphus, plus bosses Triceraton, Krang's Android and Karai. There's flying body presses, knee drops, head butts, rocket punches, elbow smashes, somersault throws, you'll feel and inflict them all. And the settings include Magma Ocean Planet, Jungle Planet, and every other bizarre corner of Dimension X!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930904T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20181223T203419</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II Turbo (U).smc</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II Turbo</name>
		<desc>Feel the Need for Speed!

They're back and they're badder than ever! Faster, stronger and with all new moves, twelve of the greatest fighters from across the globe are ready to do battle! Choose your champion and get ready for the big brawl as they try to earn the right to battle M. Bison for the title. And just when you think you've mastered it all, crank it up a notch and go TURBO!

Cover your head as Blanka dives at you from above and hear your neck crack as Zangief hits you with the Turbo Spinning Clothesline. Stare in disbelief as Dhalsim disappears before your eyes and Chun Li unleashes her blazing fireball! Watch in awe as Sagat fights Sagat and Ryu does a Hurricane Kick in mid-air! Survive all this and you may live long enough to become the greatest Street Fighter ever!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Street Fighter II Turbo (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20181224T173919</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Kart (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Super Mario Kart</name>
		<desc>The Super Mario GoKart Park is open for tons of racing fun!  Hit the track with Mario, Luigi, Yoshi and the Princess.  Get tough and lock fenders with Donkey Kong, Jr. and Bowser.  Even Toad and Koopa Troopa will mix it up in an all-out quest for the Gold Cup!  Race head-to-head with a friend or challenge the computer in great, split-screen, Mode 7 graphics.

Feel like a bit less speed and a lot more strategy?  Take a crack at the Battle Mode!  In four different maze-like courses you’ll use Koopa Shells, Banana Peels, Super Stars and other wacky weapons to burst your opponent's target balloons and triumph!

* 2 games in 1 - Mario Grand Prix and Battle Mode
* 8  Familiar Characters
* 20 Different Tracks
* 3 Different Skill Levels
* Battery-backed memory saves your best times!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario Kart (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paperboy 2 (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Paperboy 2</name>
		<desc>You're a paper boy. Get on your bicycle. Avoid obstacles on the road, such as dogs, cars, and basically everything you can imagine. Hell, some people shoot cannon balls at you! And you'd better be very sure to only throw papers at the right houses! (and at people, that's fun :)</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Paperboy 2 (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tengen</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20181226T230135</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV - Turtles in Time (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV: Turtles In Time</name>
		<desc>Sunday evening. You're sitting around the sewer watching your main reported, April O'Neil do a live remote from the Statue of Liberty. Then it happens. A humungoso flying android screams out of the sky and rips Lady Liberty from her foundation, sending hundreds of freaked out tourists into the harbor below. "No way!" cries Raphael. "Way," replies Donatello. And the crazy quantum chase is on!
Journey through ten levels of enormous arcade graphics, the largest and craziest talking Turtles ever with eons of bodacious battlegrounds, from prehistoric to futuristic galaxies. To prepare for the toughest Shred-heads you've ever seen, try the Versus mode, a Turtle-on-Turtle combat arena that finally proves who's the mightiest mutant of all. Also test your slice-em-up speed in the Time Trials mode to find out how fast you can clear three courses.
Get ready for the 3-D jab and toss that sends enemies flying right in your face. Mondo body slams and pizza power bonuses make you more Turtle than ever before. You better believe you're going to need it. Shredder's out for Turtle hide. And he's got all the time in the world to get it.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV - Turtles in Time (U) [!]-image.png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20181227T013241</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Looney Tunes B-Ball (U).smc</path>
		<name>Looney Tunes B-Ball</name>
		<desc>Looney Tunes B-Ball is a 2-on-2 Basketball game, similar to the more well known NBA Jam. However, Looney Tunes is much more informal and silly, though this level of silliness is set by the player via the Wackiness Meter on the main menu. Players choose their teams from the likes of: Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck, Elmer Fudd, Wile E. Coyote, Tasmanian Devil, Sylvester, Yosemite Sam and Marvin Martian. Each player has unique statistics for their shooting, 3-pointers, defense, stamina and speed.

Once on the court, the player can pass the ball, shoot the ball, grab a burst of speed or unleash a special defensive ability or a special offensive ability.. These abilities include cream pies, time bombs, sticks of dynamite and other fun toys from the ACME Corporation. Offensive Abilities must be "bought" by collecting gems and other items which occasionally show up on the basketball court.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Looney Tunes B-Ball (U)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<playcount>7</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190204T225934</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Attack (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Tetris Attack</name>
		<desc>The Tetris sensation has landed at Yoshi's Island. Kamek and Bowser await to test your dexterity with a demanding race of strategic moves in this exciting new contest. As the stack of perplexing panels rises from the bottom, think fast to counteract the merciless enemy attack dropping in from above. Rapid switches and quick response are the key to clearing the way to the next challenging level. An incredible selection of competitive modes and options provide escalating action and endless fun!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tetris Attack (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190209T161928</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Animaniacs (U) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Animaniacs</name>
		<desc>Animaniacs is a video game that is based on the hit animated series of the same name. Unlike regular platform games, the player usually runs from the enemies rather than fighting them. Characters include Yakko, Wakko, and Dot, Pinky and the Brain, most of the supporting cast, as well as Ralph, the Warner Brothers studio guard. Animaniacs was made into two games which bore no relation to each other in terms of gameplay, despite both being made by Konami. One was for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System and the other was for the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis and Game Boy. The SNES and Mega Drive/Genesis version were released in 1994, and the Game Boy version in 1995.</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Animaniacs (U) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190404T191015</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country (V1.1) (E).smc</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<desc>Madness and Mayhem in this 3-D Gorilla Thriller!

Donkey Kong is back with a new sidekick, Diddy Kong, in a crazy island adventure! Challenged by the crazed tribe of reptilian Kremlings, they endeavor to get back their stolen banana horde! Armed with lightning-quick moves, chest-pounding muscle and awesome aerial acrobatics, our duo is ready to face their cunning adversaries. With the help of Donkey Kong's quirky family and his wild animal mounts, they squabble and scamper their way through the unending monkey mayhem!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Donkey Kong Country (V1.1) (E)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190331T155930</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris &amp; Dr Mario (E) [!].smc</path>
		<name>Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario</name>
		<desc>The two greatest puzzle games are now together in one exciting game pak only on Super NES! TETRIS: The relentless building block video puzzle from Russia is back and enhanced for Super NES. Play solo, with a friend or challenge one of three computer opponents in this exciting and addicting game! DR. MARIO: Those nasty viruses have returned. Dr. Mario, vitamin pills in hand, is ready to eliminate them once more. In addition to the ever-popular 2-player game, now you can challenge the computer in the guise of the Blue, Yellow or Red Virus. MIXED MATCH: Combine Tetris and Dr. Mario and what do you get? One exciting contest for 2 players! Race against the clock to outscore your opponent while playing both Tetris and Dr. Mario!</desc>
		<image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tetris &amp; Dr Mario (E) [!]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>77</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20190404T221303</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
